let's talk about the fallback function
让我们来谈谈合约中的后备功能，您可以定义一个
inside the contract you can define a
special function called the fallback
称为后备功能的特殊功能，您可以像这样操作
function and you can do it like this the
function cannot have a name it cannot
函数不能具有名称，不能接受任何输入，也不能返回任何名称
take any inputs and it cannot return any
output and they must be declared as
输出，并且必须将它们声明为外部，现在此函数将是
external now this function will be
called in two situations one when you
在两种情况下调用：一种是在您调用不存在的函数时-当
call function that does not exist - when
you send either to this contract by sand
您可以通过沙沙转移或致电发送给该合同，并为此
transfer or call and in order for this
contract to receive either the fallback
接受后备功能的合同必须声明为应付账款，并且
function must be declared as payable and
inside the function you can write your
在函数内部，您可以像常规函数一样在此处编写代码，但是它
code here like a regular function but it
is recommended not to write almost any
建议不要在其中写任何代码，原因是
code inside here the reason is that when
you send either by hand or transfer it
您可以手动发送或转移2300次喘息-这种后备
for its 2300 gasps - this fallback
function which is enough gas to email or
该功能足以发送电子邮件或日志，但没有足够的电量来写入
log but not enough gas to write to
storage or call another contract and to
存储或调用其他合同，并向您显示转发和转移
show you that send and transfer forwards
2300 gas we're gonna use a special
2300汽油我们将在这里使用一种特殊的功能，称为汽油剩余
function here called gas left that
returns the remaining gas and we'll
返回剩余的气体，我们将更新dog事件以返回
update our dog event to return the
amount of gas left we'll also create a
剩余的气体量，我们还将创建一个辅助函数，以返回余额
helper function that returns the balance
of ether stored in this contract next
储存在该合约中的以太币接下来，我们将创建一个合约
we're going to create a contract that
will send either to the contract above
将发送给以上合同，这将触发后备功能
which will trigger the fallback function
the first function that we're going to
我们将要创建的第一个函数称为转移下降
create will be called transfer to fall
back after we deployed these two
在我们将这两个合同部署到这里之后，我们将通过
contracts here we're going to pass in
the address of the fallback contract
以上备用合同的地址，我们将使用
above and we're gonna send either using
the transfer method transfer forwards
转移方法转移2300瓦斯，之后当我们实际呼叫时
2300 gas and later when we actually call
this function here you'll be able to see
使用此功能，您现在可以看到剩余气体少于2300
that the gas left is less than 2300 now
recall that sending neeterb like all
回想一下，像福特一样向所有公司派遣neeterb的所有气体
Ford's all the gas to the fallback
function and in that case gas theft can
功能，在这种情况下，煤气盗窃可能会超过2300，并向您显示
be greater than 2300 and to show you a
demo of this we're going to create a
此演示我们将创建一个函数，该函数将调用
function that's going to call the
fallback contract above using the call
使用调用的后备合同，我们将此函数命名为
and we'll name this function call
fallback
后备广告，我们将使用call方法发送
we'll send either using the call method
and make sure that it was able to send
并确保它能够发送食者
the eater
now let's deploy the contract execute
现在让我们部署合同来执行功能，我将逐步指导您
the functions and I'll walk you through
how the codes are executed
代码如何执行
so here I've deployed the two contracts
所以在这里，我部署了两个合同，即后备合同
the fallback contract that's going to be
receiving the ETA and sent to for that
接收预计到达时间并发送给该合同的合同，该合同将发送
contract that's going to be sending the
heater and let's go over the transfer to
加热器，让我们先谈谈向后备功能的转移，我要
fallback function first so I'm gonna
copy and paste the address of the
在此处复制并粘贴后备合同的地址，然后发送一个
fallback contract here and send one
either when we check the transaction log
或者当我们检查交易记录时，您可以在此处看到记录为2255
you can see here that it logged 2255
gasp so when we call the transfer to
喘着粗气，所以当我们调用转移到后备功能时，它将以太发送到
fallback function it sent the ether to
the fallback contract above using the
上面的后备合同使用转移方法触发了
transfer method which triggered the
fallback function inside the fallback
后备合同内的后备功能，以及自转移以来
contract and since transfer forwards
2300 gas by the time the cold reached
到这里的冷气到达2300瓦斯时，它已经使用了一些瓦斯和瓦斯
here it used some of the gas and gas
theft returned an amount less than 2300
盗窃返回的金额小于2300，在这种情况下，下一个我返回2255
in this case it returned 2255 next I
want to show you that the call method is
想要告诉您调用方法将转发所有气体，所以再次
going to forward all of the gas so again
I'm gonna copy the address of the
我要在此处复制后备合同的地址，然后发送一个
fallback contract here and then send one
ether again
再次以太
and let's check the transaction log then
让我们检查事务日志，然后您可以在此处看到它转发了更多内容
you can see here that it forwarded more
than two thousand three hundred gasps
超过23300次喘息，与之前的示例类似
similar to the previous example when we
called the function called fallback this
称为回退功能，此功能将以太币发送至回退合约
sent the ethers to the fallback contract
by the call method which forwarded all
通过转发所有喘气的调用方法，回退功能是
of the gasps the fallback function was
executed and involved the remaining gas
执行并涉及剩余的天然气，这是这里的数量，因此总之
which is this amount here so in summary
the fallback function receives two
备用功能在收到后会收到两千三百次喘息
thousand three hundred gasps when it is
invoked by the send or transfer method
由send或transfer方法调用，但在发送时可以接收更多气体
but it can receive more gas when it is
invoked by the call method the call
通过call方法调用，call方法可以将所有气体提供给
method can afford all of the gas to the
fallback function which means that you
后备功能，这意味着您可以像编写常规功能一样编写代码
can write code like a regular function
to execute inside the fallback function
在后备功能内执行，但建议不要写太多
but it is recommended not to write much
cold inside it since the function can
内部温度过低，因为如果使用过多的气体，该功能可能会失败，这意味着
fail if it uses too much gas which means
that you won't be able to send either to
您将无法使用“发送”或“转移”将其发送到合同
the contract using the send or transfer
method so that's all I got for this
方法，如果您有任何问题，请放心，这就是我为这部影片所拍摄的全部内容
video if you have any questions let me
know in the comments below have a nice
知道在下面的评论中度过了愉快的一天，我很快会在下一个与您见面
day and I'll see you soon in the next
video
视频